

## **Profile**

Motivated and self-taught Web Developer with a true passion for technology. Offering over nine years of professional experience in managing front- and back-end projects. A team player who enjoys collaborating with others, regardless of backgrounds, to deliver meaningful and accessible experiences. Goal-oriented and positive attitude, and the desire to provide excellent support, service, and solutions to customers. Strong programming fundamentals and the ability to quickly learn new skills and apply successful strategies with energy and a professional demeanor.

## **Employment History**

#### Senior Consultant, Sogeti, USA, Cincinnati

OCTOBER 2018 - PRESENT

- Proctor & Gamble unit project lead, using agile scrum methodology and rightshore resources to test and deliver swift, lean updates
- Developed in React, Azure, Node, and JavaScript to build new and unique solutions for client needs, like iOS apps and facial recognition
- Google Analytics Certified and a unit recognized delivery excellence award recipient
- Volunteer through employee affinity groups, company hackathons, and leading skillshare virtual trainings

#### Senior Website Programmer, United States Dressage Federation, Lexington

JULY 2011 - OCTOBER 2018

- Web and database administrator using ASP/SQL
- E-commerce, email marketing, reporting
- Social media and publications solution provider
- Onsite AV and staff IT support

#### Volleyball Official, USA Volleyball, Lexington

JANUARY 2012 - PRESENT

- OH/KY High School Athletic Association Volleyball Official
- Two-time High School State Tournament official
- 2017 Official of the Year for the state of Kentucky
- 2015 Louis Seelbach Award Winner (Central Kentucky Volleyball Official Association)
- USAV Junior National certified official

# Customer Service Representative, Carnegie Museums of Art and Natural History, Pittsburgh

OCTOBER 2007 - JUNE 2011

- Coordinated front desk ticket sales, visitor relations, and temporary exhibition maintenance
- Trained new employees in Paciolan ticket reservation system, switchboard operations, group registration, membership sales, and greeting

## **Education**

## Bachelor of Science, Stanford University, Palo Alto

2003 - 2007

## **Details**

White Salmon, 98672, United States 724-581-1581

bdejesus@alumni.stanford.edu

NATIONALITY

American

## Links

**Portfolio** 

## Languages

ReactJS

Azure

Node

Git

Python

Angular

O365

Google Analytics

#### Hobbies

Volleyball, hiking, movies, cooking, traveling

- Majored in Symbolic Systems with a concentration in Philosophical Foundations
- Core curriculum in computer science, logic, & linguistics

## Associate Degree, Pittsburgh Technical Institute, Pittsburgh

2010 - 2012

- Associate in Science, Information Technology
- JavaScript and Systems Administration

## Web Design Immersive, General Assembly, New York City

FEBRUARY 2017 - MAY 2017

• Fullstack coding bootcamp in JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, and ReactJS

## Extra-curricular activities

## President, Central Kentucky Volleyball Officials Association, Lexington

NOVEMBER 2017 - NOVEMBER 2018

Official spokesperson for Lexington, KY area high school volleyball officials.

## Sports Commissioner, Bluegrass State Games, Lexington

FEBRUARY 2013 - AUGUST 2015

Directed tournament scheduling, site coordination, event registration, marketing, and volunteer recruiting.

# Internships

### Web Design Intern, Magee-Womens Foundation, Pittsburgh

JANUARY 2009 - FEBRUARY 2010

Worked as lead designer and developer for Dan Berger Cord Blood Donation program website.